Finding aid for the Hearst Corporation Los Angeles Examiner photographs, negatives and clippings - oversize portrait and subject files 7000.3
USC Libraries Special Collections
- Oversize Portrait Files
  - G
    - Gollum, Geo (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Gomez -- Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Gonzales, Richard (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Gonzalez -- Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Goo- (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Goodale -- Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Goodrich -- Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Goodwin -- Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Gop-Gq (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Gordon -- Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Gottwald, Klement (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Gould -- Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Gra-Grd (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Grable, Betty (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Grady -- Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Graham-E -- Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Graham, Barbara (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Graham, Billy (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Grahame, Gloria -- Actress (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Granger, Farlax (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Granger, Stewart (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Grant -- Miscellaneous (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Grant, Cary (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Granville, Bonita (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Grauman, Sid (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Graves -- Miscellaneous (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Gray -- Miscellaneous (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Gray, Colleen (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Gray, Gilda (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Grayson, Kathryn (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Graziano, Rocky (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Gre-Grez (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Greece -- Royalty (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Green -- Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Green, William -- AFL Leader (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Greenberg -- Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Greene -- Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Greene, Richard -- Actor (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Greenwood, Charlotte (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Greer, Jane -- Actress (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Grey, Virginia (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Gri-Gt (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Griffin -- Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Griffis -- Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Griffith -- Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Grimm -- Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Groesz -- Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Gromyko, Andre (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Groom -- Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Gross -- Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Groves -- Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Gu-Gz (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Gubitchev, Valentin (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Guild, Nancy (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Gunderson -- Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Guzik -- Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Gwynne, Anne (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - H
    - Haa-Hab (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Hac (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Had-Haf (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Hadley, Carleton S. -- Mrs. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Hag (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Hah-Hak (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Haines -- Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Hala-Hallh (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Hale -- Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Hale, Barbara (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Haley -- Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Hall -- Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Hall, Jon (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Halli-Hallz (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Halm-Halz (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Halsey, William F., Admiral (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Hama-Haml (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton, A-Z (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Hamm (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Hamn-Hamz (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Hampton, Hope (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Hana-Hanm (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Hann-Hanz (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Hannegan, Robert (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Hansen, A-Z (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Hanson -- Miscellaneous (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Hanson, Beverly -- Golfer (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Hao-Haq (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Hara-Hard (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Harding, Ann (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Hardy -- Miscellaneous (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Hare-Harf (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Harg-Hark (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Hargrove -- Miscellaneous (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Harl-Harq (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Harmon -- Miscellaneous (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Harr-Harz (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Harridge -- Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Harriman -- Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Harris, A-Z (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Harris, Phil (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Harris, Stanley -- "Bucky" -- Baseball (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Harrison -- Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Harrison, William H. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Hart -- Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Hartford, Huntington III -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Hartley -- Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Hartman -- Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Harvey -- Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Has-Hat (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Hass, Fred Jr. -- Golf (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Hasso, Signe -- Actress (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Hastings -- Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Hastings, Margaret -- Shangri-la Diary (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Hatfield -- Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Hau-Hav (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Hauser -- Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Haver, June -- Actress (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Havoc, June (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Haw-Haz (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Hawkins -- Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Hawks, Hawkes -- Miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue -- Actor (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Hayden, Haydon -- Miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Hayes, Hays -- Miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Haymes, Dick -- Singer (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Haynes -- Miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Hayward -- Miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Hayward, Louis (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Hayward, Susan (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Hayworth, Rita -- Groups -- Not Including Aly Khan (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Hayworth, Rita -- Heads and Alone (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Hayworth, Rita -- Wedding Pictures Only (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Hayworth, Rita -- With Aly -- Before and After Wedding (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Hayworth, Rita -- With Yasmine and Rebecca Welles Only (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Hea-Heb (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Hearst, William Randolph Jr. -- And Mrs. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Heath, Jeff (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Hec-Hed (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Hee-Heg (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Heflin, Van (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Heh-Her (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Heirens, William -- Degnan Suspect (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Hel-Hem (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Hellinger -- Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Helser, Brenda (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Hemingway -- Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Hen-Hep (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Henderson -- Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Hendrix, Wanda (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Henie, Sonja (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Henreid, Paul (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Henn -- Quadruplets (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Henrich, Tommy (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Henry -- Miscellaneous (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Hepburn, Katharine (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Her (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Herbert, A-Z (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Herman-- Miscellaneous (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Hershey, Lewis B. -- General (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Hersholt, Jean -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Hes (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Het-Hez (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Hia-Hik (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Hickenlooper, Bourke B. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Hickey -- Miscellaneous (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Higgins -- Miscellaneous (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Hil-Him (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Hildreth -- Miscellaneous (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Hill -- Miscellaneous (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Hill, Virginia -- Siegel Case (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Hilton -- Miscellaneous (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Hin (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Hines -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Hir-Hj (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Hiss, Alger (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Hitchcock -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Hitler, Adolf (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Hodes -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Hodgdon -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Hodges -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Hodiak -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 8 - 9)
    - Hodiak, John -- And Wife (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Hoerner -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Hoey -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Hoffman -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Hogan -- Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Hogan, Ben -- Golfer (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Hohenlohe (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Holden -- Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Holden, William (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Holifield -- Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Holland -- Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Holland -- Miscellaneous -- Royalty (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Holliday -- Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Holliday, Judy (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Holm, Celeste - Actress (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Holman -- Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Holman, Libby (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Holmes -- Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Holohan -- Miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Holscher -- Miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Holt -- Miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Honeycutt -- Miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Hook, Davey (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Hoover -- Miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Hoover, Herbert -- Miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Hop-Hopz (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Hope, Bob -- Alone and Groups of Two -- And Mrs. (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Hope, Bob -- Groups of Three or More (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Hopkins -- Miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Hopkins, Miriam (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Hopp -- Miscellaneous (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Horn, Horne -- Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Hornbostel -- Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Horner -- Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Horner, Jackie -- Prodigy (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Horton -- Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Hotchkiss -- Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Howard -- Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Howe -- Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Hq-Ht (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Hsiu-Chuan, Wu (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Hu-Hz (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Hubbard -- Miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Hudson -- Miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Hudson, Rock -- Actor (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Hughes -- Miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Hughes, Howard (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Hull -- Miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Hull, Patricia Jean -- Slain Ten-Year-Old Girl -- And Parents, Grandparents, Uncle (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Humphrey, Humphreys -- Miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Hunt -- Miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Hunt, Marsha (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Hunter -- Miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Hussey, Ruth (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Huston, Walter (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Hutchins, Colleen Kay (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Hutton -- Miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Hutton, Barbara (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Hutton, Betty (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Hutton, Robert "Bob" (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Hyatt, John R. -- Mr. and Mrs. -- And Family (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Hyer, Martha -- Actress (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - I-J
    - I-Iz (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Ickes, Harold L. (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Il, Nam, General -- China Red (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Impellitteri, Vincent (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - India -- Personal Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Indore -- Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Ingalls -- Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Ingersoll, Felice (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Ingram -- Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Inverchapel, Lord (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Ipar, Ali (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Iran -- Personal Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Iran -- Shah Reza Pahlevi (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Ireland, John (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Irvine -- Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Irving -- Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Irwin -- Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Isaacs -- Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Italy -- Personal Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Italy -- Royalty (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Ivers, Alwyn "Sonny" -- And Wife Betty (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Ives -- Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Ja-Jan (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Jackson -- Miscellaneous (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Jackson, Felix (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Jackson, Robert (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Jacobs -- Miscellaneous (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Jacobson -- Miscellaneous (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Jagger, Dean (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - James -- Miscellaneous (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Jan-Jaz (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Janis, Elsie (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Jansen, Larry -- Baseball (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Japan -- Emperor Hirohito (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Japan -- Miscellaneous (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Japan -- Peace Conference and Treaty (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Japan -- Royalty (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Japan -- Tokyo (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Jarman -- Miscellaneous (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Jb-Jn (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Jebb, Gladwyn, Sir (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Jeffers -- Miscellaneous (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Jefferson -- Miscellaneous (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Jeffreys -- Miscellaneous (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Jeffreys, Anne -- Actress (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Jenkins -- Miscellaneous (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Jennings -- Miscellaneous (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Jensen -- Miscellaneous (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Jensen, Jackie -- Baseball -- Former All-American (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Jessel, George (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Jessup, Philip C. -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Jewell -- Miscellaneous (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Jo-Jz (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Johansson, Ingemar -- Boxer (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - John, Pope XXII -- Obituary (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - John, Pope XXIII (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Johnson -- Miscellaneous (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Louis A. (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Rita -- In Oygen Tent (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Van -- Actor (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Johnston -- Miscellaneous (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Johnston, Alvanley (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Johnston, Eric (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Johnston, Johnny (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Jolson, Al (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Jones -- Miscellaneous (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Jones, A (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Jones, B (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Jones, C (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Jones, D (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Jones, J (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Jennifer (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Jones, M (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Jones, R (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Jones, S (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Shirley (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Spike -- And Family (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Jordan -- Miscellaneous (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Jourdan, Louis (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Joy, C. Turner Adm. (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Joy, Leatrice -- Actress (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Joyce -- Miscellaneous (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Joyce, Brenda -- Actress (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Joyce, Peggy Hopkins (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Judge, Arline (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Jurado, Katy (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - K
    - Kaa-Kaz (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Kai-Shek, Chiang -- Gen. and Mme. (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Kai-Shek, Chiang Mme. (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Kaiser -- Miscellaneous (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Kaiser, Henry Jr. - Sr. (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Kane -- Miscellaneous (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Karloff, Boris (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Kasenkina, Oksana -- Mrs. (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Kashfi, Anna -- Actress (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Kaufman, Kauffman -- Miscellaneous (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Kaye, Danny -- Actor, And Family (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Kea-Kei (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Keane -- Miscellaneous (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Kearns -- Miscellaneous (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Kee, John (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Keel, Howard (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Keenan -- Miscellaneous (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Kefauver, Estes (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Kej-Kel (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Kellems, Vivian (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Keller -- Miscellaneous (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Kelley -- Miscellaneous (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Kelly -- Miscellaneous, A-D (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Kelly, E-L (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Kelly, Gene (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Kelly, Grace -- Special Feature Pictures (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Kelly, M-Z (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Kelton, Pert -- Actress (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy -- Miscellaneous (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, John F. -- President (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy, John F. -- President (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy, John F. -- Senator (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Kenny, Elizabeth -- Sister (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Kenny, Kenney -- Miscellaneous (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Kent -- Miscellaneous (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Keq-Ker (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Kerr -- Miscellaneous (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Kerr, Deborah (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Kes-Kez (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Keyes, Evelyn (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Kh-Kn (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Khan -- Miscellaneous (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Khan, Aga (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Khan, Aly - And Rita (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita -- Russian Premier (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita -- U.S. Tour (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Kil-Kiq (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Kilgallen, Dorothy (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Kilgore -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Kilpatrick -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Kilroy -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Kim -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Kimmel -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Kiner, Ralph (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - King -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - King, Andrea (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - King, Ernest J. -- Adm. (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - King, Mackenzie (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Kinkaid, Kincaid -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Kinney -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Kir-Kiz (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Kirk -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Kirkwood -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Kirsten -- Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - Kj-Kl (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Klein -- Miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Klotz, Herbie (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Km-Kn (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Kmiec, Andrew (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Knapp -- Miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Knauf -- Miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Knight -- Miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Knight, Goodwin J. -- Alone (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Knight, Goodwin J. -- And Family (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Knight, Goodwin J. -- And Wife (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Knight, Goodwin J. -- Groups (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Knight, June (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Knowland -- Miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Knowland, William F. -- Senator (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Knox -- Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Knudsen, Knudson -- Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Knutson -- Miscellaneous (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Koa-Kol (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Koch, Ilse (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Kom-Koz (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Konstanty, Jim (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Koo, Wellington (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Korvin, Charles (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Kosenkina, Okana (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Kramer -- Miscellaneous (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Krueger, Kruger -- Miscellaneous (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Krug -- Miscellaneous (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Kubon -- Miscellaneous (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Kuhn -- Miscellaneous (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Kuusela, Armi -- Miss Universe (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Kyser, Kay -- And Mrs. (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - L
    - La-Lam (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Ladd, Alan -- Actor (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - LaForce, Richard C. (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - LaGuardia, Fiorella (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Lake -- Miscellaneous (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Lake, Arthur -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Lake, Veronica (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Lamarr, Hedy (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Lamarre, Bleriot -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Lamas, Fernando (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Lambert -- Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Lamotta, Jake -- Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Lamour, Dorothy (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Lampe -- Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Lamphere -- Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Lan-Lap (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Lancaster -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Land -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Landis, Carole (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Lane -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Lane, Priscilla and Rosemary (Sisters) -- Actresses (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Lang -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Langan -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Langdon, Harry (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Lange -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Langford, Frances (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Lanham -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Lanier -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Lansbury -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Lansbury, Angela (Box 104, Folder 15 - 18)
    - Lanza, Mario -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Laphon -- Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Lar-Laz (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Larsen, Arthur -- Tennis (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Larsen, Larson -- Miscellaneous (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Lattimore, Owen J. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Laughton, Charles (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Laurel, Stan (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Laurie, Piper -- Actress (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Laval, Pierre (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Lawford -- Miscellaneous (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Lawrence -- Miscellaneous (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Lawrence, Betty -- Track (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Lawson -- Miscellaneous (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Lea (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Leahy -- Miscellaneous (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Leahy, Frank (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Leb-Lec (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Led-Leg (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Lederer, Francis -- Actor (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Lee -- Miscellaneous (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Lee, Anna -- Actress (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Lee, Gwen -- Actress (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Lee, Peggy -- Actress (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Leeds -- Miscellaneous (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Leeds, Andrea -- Actress (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Leeds, Lila (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Leh (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Lehman, Herbert H., Senator (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Lei-Lel (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Leigh, Janet -- Actress (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Leigh, Vivian -- Actress (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Lem-Lenz (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Lemmon, Jack -- Film actor (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Len-Lenz (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Lenorak, Lillian -- Murdered (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Leo-Let (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Leonard -- Miscellaneous (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Leslie, Joan -- Actress (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Lesnevich, Gus -- Boxer (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Leu-Lez (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Levy -- Miscellaneous (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Lewis -- Miscellaneous (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Lewis, "Strangler" (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Lewis, Clyde A. (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Lewis, Jerry (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Lewis, John L. -- Labor (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Monica (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, Tom (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Lh-Lil (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Lie, Trygve (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Lilienthal -- Miscellaneous (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Lilienthal, David (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Lillie, Beatrice (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Lim-Liz (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Limb, Ben C. (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln -- Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Little -- Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Llo-Lop (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Lloyd -- Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Lloyd, Harold (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Locke, Bobby -- Golfer (Box 110, Folder 4)